Preliminary Guide to the Mutual Broadcasting System, Inc. records, 1952-2000 MS2083
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Mutual Broadcasting System, Inc. records
1952-2000
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Mutual Broadcasting System
Walker, Mike (Brian E.)
King, Larry
Bohannon, Jim
MS2083
1354 Linear Feet
The Mutual Broadcasting System, Inc. records contain more than 40,000 sound recordings, primarily in audiocassette and reel-to-reel audiotape format, as well as scripts and other supporting documents generated by the various shows produced by the Mutual Broadcasting System from the 1950's through the 1990's, including the Jim Bohannon show, 1993-2000; America this week, 1990-2000; First light, 1990-2000; Mike Walker show, 1990-1995; The week in review, 1984-2000; Seems like yesterday (SLY), 1987-1989; Weekend headliners, 1987-1999; Newsbreakers, 1985-1990; America in the morning, 1984-2000; The week in review, 1983-1992; Larry King show, 1980-[199-?]; Mutual Broadcasting series, 1980-1999; NBC extra, 1980-1998; Larry King show (Miami years), 1970-1979; Mutual Radio theater/Zero hour, 1970-1979; and The World today, 1958-1982. The collection also includes an extensive collection of phonographic recordings of music that had been played over the MBS, obituaries, and reports.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Westwood One, Inc., 2000.
Historical Note
The Mutual Broadcasting System (MBS) was an American radio network, in operation from 1934 to 1999. A more detailed historical note should be written when the collection is processed. At this time a lengthy article can be found in Wikipedia. (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mutual_Radio_Network)
Collection Scope and Content
The Mutual Broadcasting System, Inc. records contain more than 40,000 sound recordings, primarily in audiocassette and reel-to-reel audiotape format, as well as scripts and other supporting documents generated by the various shows produced by the Mutual Broadcasting System from the 1950's through the 1990's, including the Jim Bohannon show, 1993-2000; America this week, 1990-2000; First light, 1990-2000; Mike Walker show, 1990-1995; The week in review, 1984-2000; Seems like yesterday (SLY), 1987-1989; Weekend headliners, 1987-1999; Newsbreakers, 1985-1990; America in the morning, 1984-2000; The week in review, 1983-1992; Larry King show, 1980-[199-?]; Mutual Broadcasting series, 1980-1999; NBC extra, 1980-1998; Larry King show (Miami years), 1970-1979; Mutual Radio theater/Zero hour, 1970-1979; and The World today, 1958-1982. The collection also includes an extensive collection of phonographic recordings of music that had been played over the MBS, obituaries, and reports.
This collection is not processed. Please see staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
Collection is organized into multiple series: O.J. Simpson trial, 1994-1998; Jim Bohannon show, 1993-2000; President Bill Clinton, 1993-1998; Persian Gulf war, 1991; Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas hearings, 1991; America this week, 1990-2000; First light, 1990-2000; Mike Walker show, 1990-1995; President George Bush, 1989-1992; The week in review, 1984-2000; Seems like yesterday (SLY), 1987-1989; Weekend headliners, 1987-1999; Newsbreakers, 1985-1990; America in the morning, 1984-2000; The week in review scripts, 1984-1996; The week in review, 1983-1992; Iranian Hostages return, 1981; President Reagan cabinet confirmation hearings, 1981; President Ronald Reagan, 1981-1986; Golden reels/Golden cassettes, 1980-1998; Golden reels/Golden cassettes finding aids ("Golden Sheets"), 1980-1998; Larry King show, 1980-[199-?]; Larry King show program log, 1980-[199-?]; Mutual Broadcasting series, 1980-1999; NBC extra, 1980-1998; Political conventions, 1980; RKO cut sheets, 1980-1989; RKO morgue, 1980-1989; The world this morning, 1978-1982; Reporter roundup, 1976-1988; Jackie Robinson, Women in the military, and Miscellaneous tapes, [ca. 1970-1981]; Larry King show (Miami years), 1970-1979; Miscellaneous unlabeled tapes, 1970-1989; Mutual Radio theater/Zero hour, 1970-1979; Special events, 1963-1998; Political/Historical events, 1960-1985; The World today, 1958-1982; NBC sound bites; Obituaries; Source reports; Phonograph collection; Mutual News; Network tape files
Phonograph records; Audiocassettes; Audiotapes; Diaries
- Mutual Radio Theater/Zero Hour, Circa 1973-1980; Series 1; 31.5 Linear Feet
  - Mutual Radio Theater closet, Series 1 (Box 1)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/17/1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 1)
    General Note
    Item Title: Week 1, #1, "The Wife of the Red-Haired Man" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/18/1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 2)
    Item Title: Week 1, #2 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 12/14/1973
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/19/1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 3)
    Item Title: Week 1, #3 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 12/16/1973
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/20/1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 4)
    Item Title: Week 1, #4 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 12/20/1973
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/21/1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 5)
    Item Title: Week 1, #5 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/24/1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 6)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 12/17/1973
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/25/1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 7)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 12/18/1973
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/26/1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 8)
    Item Title: Week 2, #3 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 12/18/1973
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/27/1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 9)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 12/19/1973
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/28/1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 10)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 12/31/1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 11)
    Item Title: Week 3 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 12/19/1973
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/1/1974; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 12)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 12/20/1973
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/2/1974; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 13)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/3/1974; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 14)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/4/1974; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 15)
    Item Title: Week 3, #5 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 12/21/1973
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/7/1974; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 16)
    Item Title: Week 4, #1 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 01/02/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/7/1974; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 17)
    Item Title: Week 4, #1 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/8/1974; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 18)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 01/02/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/8/1974; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 19)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/9/1974; Series 1 (Box 1, Reel 20)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Prot. Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 01/02/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/9/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 21)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/10/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 22)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 01/03/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/10/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 23)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/11/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 24)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/11/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 25)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/14/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 26)
    Item Title: Week 5 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/14/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 27)
    Item Title: Week 5 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 7:00pm Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/15/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 28)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 7:00pm Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/15/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 29)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/16/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 30)
    Item Title: Week 5, #3 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 01/08/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/16/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 31)
    Item Title: Week 5, #3 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/17/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 32)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/17/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 33)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 01/08/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/18/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 34)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/18/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 35)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/21/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 36)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/22/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 37)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/23/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 38)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/24/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 39)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/25/1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Reel 40)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/28/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 41)
    Item Title: Week 7 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 01/16/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/29/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 42)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 01/17/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/30/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 43)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 01/18/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 1/31/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 44)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 01/21/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/1/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 45)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 01/23/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/4/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 46)
    Item Title: Week 8 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/5/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 47)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/6/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 48)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/7/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 49)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/8/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 50)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 01/28/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/11/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 51)
    Item Title: Week 9, #1 "Someone's Death" Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 01/30/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/12/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 52)
    Item Title: Week 9, #2 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 01/31/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/13/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 53)
    Item Title: Week 9, #3 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 01/31/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/14/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 54)
    Item Title: Week 9, #4 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 02/01/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/15/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 55)
    Item Title: Week 9, #5 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/18/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 56)
    Item Title: Week 10 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 02/05/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/18/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 57)
    Item Title: Week 10 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/19/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 58)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Copy #2 Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 02/06/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/19/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 59)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 02/06/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/20/1974; Series 1 (Box 3, Reel 60)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/20/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 61)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 02/07/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/21/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 62)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/21/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 63)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 02/08/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/22/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 64)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 02/11/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/22/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 65)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/24/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 66)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/25/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 67)
    Item Title: Week 11 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 02/12/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/25/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 68)
    Item Title: Week 11 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/26/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 69)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 02/14/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/26/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 70)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/27/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 71)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/27/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 72)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/28/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 73)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 02/15/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/1/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 74)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/1/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 75)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 02/19/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/4/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 76)
    Item Title: Week 12 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 02/04/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/5/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 77)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 02/25/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/6/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 78)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/7/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 79)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 02/26/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/8/1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Reel 80)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/11/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 81)
    Item Title: Week 13, #1 "Queen in Danger" Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 03/05/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/12/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 82)
    Item Title: Week 13, #2 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 03/05/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/13/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 83)
    Item Title: Week 13, #3 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 03/05/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/14/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 84)
    Item Title: Week 13, #4 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 03/04/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/15/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 85)
    Item Title: Week 13, #5 "Queen in Danger" Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 03/04/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/18/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 86)
    Item Title: Week 14 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/19/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 87)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 03/08/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/20/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 88)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/21/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 89)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/22/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 90)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/25/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 91)
    Item Title: Week 15 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/25/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 92)
    Item Title: Week 15 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 03/12/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/26/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 93)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/26/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 94)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 03/12/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/27/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 95)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/27/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 96)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/28/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 97)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/28/1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Reel 98)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/29/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 99)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/29/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 100)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/1/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 101)
    Item Title: Week 16 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/1/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 102)
    Item Title: Week 16 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 03/19/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/2/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 103)
    Item Title: Week 16 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 03/20/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/2/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 104)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/3/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 105)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 03/20/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/3/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 106)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/4/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 107)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/4/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 108)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/5/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 109)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/5/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 110)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 03/21/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/8/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 111)
    Item Title: Week 17 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 04/01/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/8/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 112)
    Item Title: Week 17 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/9/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 113)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/9/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 114)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/10/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 115)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/10/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 116)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 04/01/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/11/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 117)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/11/1974; Series 1 (Box 6, Reel 118)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/12/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 119)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/12/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 120)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/14/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 121)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/15/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 122)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/15/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 123)
    Item Title: Week 8 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 04/08/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/16/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 124)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/16/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 125)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 04/08/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/17/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 126)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/17/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 127)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/18/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 128)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/19/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 129)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/18/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 130)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/19/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 131)
    Item Title: Week 8, #5 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/22/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 132)
    Item Title: Week 6 Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 04/06/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/23/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 133)
    Item Title: unknown Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 04/16/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/24/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 134)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/25/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 135)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/26/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 136)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/29/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 137)
    Item Title: Week 1, #1 "Bye, Bye Narco" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/29/1974; Series 1 (Box 7, Reel 138)
    Item Title: Week 1, #1 "Bye, Bye Narco" Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 0.795138888888889 Date Recorded: 04/26/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/30/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 139)
    Item Title: Week 1, #2 "Terror in the Night" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/30/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 140)
    Item Title: Week 1, #2 "Terror in the Night" Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 04/30/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/1/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 141)
    Item Title: Week 1, #3 "Scream of the Hawk" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/1/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 142)
    Item Title: Week 1, #3 "Scream of the Hawk" Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 04/25/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/2/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 143)
    Item Title: Week 1, #4 "The Extortionist" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/2/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 144)
    Item Title: Week 1, #4 "The Extortionist" Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 04/26/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/3/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 145)
    Item Title: Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/6/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 146)
    Item Title: Week 2, #6 "A Shortage Story" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/6/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 147)
    Item Title: Week 2, #6 "A Shortage Story" Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 05/01/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/7/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 148)
    Item Title: Week 2, #7 "Escape to Nowhere" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/7/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 149)
    Item Title: Week 2, #7 "Escape to Nowhere" Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 7:00-7:29:30pm Date Recorded: 05/01/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/8/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 150)
    Item Title: Week 2, #8 "Fair's Fair, You Know" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/8/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 151)
    Item Title: Week 2, #8 "Fair's Fair, You Know" Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10am, 7:05:10pm, 10:05:10pm Date Recorded: 05/01/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/9/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 152)
    Item Title: Week 2, #9 "The House Call" Copy Details: Air Copy Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10-11:28:40am, 7:05:10-7:28:40pm, 10:05:10-10:28:40pm Date Recorded: 05/01/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 5/9/1974; Series 1 (Box 8, Reel 153)